♪ Don't go
breaking my heart ♪
Anybody do "Walking
on Sunshine" yet?
(Sheldon:)No.
(Stuart:)Dibs.
(Priya:)I'm sorry, Sheldon
bought a loom
(Priya:)and learned
how to weave?
(Leonard:)He actually
got pretty good.
(Leonard:)He made us
all matching serapes.
(Raj:)I still wear mine
when there's a nip in the air.
(Priya:)Now, was this before
(Priya:)or after he adopted
the 25 cats?
(Leonard:)Long before the cats.
(Leonard:)I think it was
around the time he tried
(Leonard:)to declare our apartment
a sovereign nation.
(Leonard:)I still have some
of the currency.
(knocking at door)
SHELDON:
All my friends.
(Sheldon(outside):)All my friends.
(Howard:)I think it's like Beetlejuice.
(Howard:)We said his name too many times.
(Penny:)Come on in.
Thank you.
(Leonard:)Hey. I thought you were
with your new buddies.
(Sheldon:)I had to leave.